Up to this point, we haven't spoken much about object-oriented Python.
至此，我們還沒有講太多的物件導向(object-oriented)程式設計的Python。
While functions play a big role in the Python ecosystem, Python does have classes
雖然函數在Python生態系統中扮演重要角色，但Python確實具有類別(classes)
which can have attached methods, and be instantiated as objects.
可以有附加的方法(method)，並被具現化為物件(object)。
Now, this course isn't about the nitty-gritty details of objects in Python,
現在，這門課程並不是關於在Python中，物件的細節
or object-oriented programming.
或物件導向的程式設計。
And actually, while you'll use objects a lot in Python,
實際上，雖然你將在Python中使用很多物件(object)，
you're less likely to be creating new classes when you use the interactive
你是不太可能會創建新的class，當您使用互動式
environment, because it's a bit verbose.
環境，因為它是有點太詳細冗長。
But I think it's important to go over a few details of objects in Python, just so
但是，我認為重要的是要在Python中了解一些object的細節，
that you aren't surprised when you see them.
以便您在看到它們時不感到驚訝。
First, you can define a class using a class keyword, and ending with a colon.
首先，你可以定義一個class，使用class關鍵字，並以冒號結尾。
Anything indented below this, is within the scope of the class.
任何縮進低於此，是在class的範圍內。
Classes in Python are generally named using camel case,
在Python中class的名稱一般稱使用camel大小寫，
which means the first character of each word is capitalized.
這意味著每個單詞的第一個字元用大寫。
You don't declare variables within the object, you just start using them.
您不需要在物件中聲明變數，您只需開始使用它們。
Class variables can also be declared.
此外class的變數可以被聲明。
These are just variables which are shared across all instances.
這些只是在所有實例(instances)之間共享的變數。
So in this example, we're saying that the default for
所以我們說，在此示例中，預設值為
all people is at the school of information.
所有人都是屬於資訊學校。
It's not very useful here, but I wanted to show it for completeness.
在這裡，不是很有用，但我要顯示是為了它的完整性。
To define a method, you just write it as you would have a function.
要定義一種方法(method)，你只要寫它像你寫函數(function)一樣。
The one change, is that to have access to the instance which a method is
一個不同的是，要能夠使用實例，在其中這一方法
being invoked upon, you must include self, in the method signature.
被援引的，你必須在方法的簽名中包含self.。
Similarly, if you want to refer to instance variables set on the object,
同樣，如果你想引用實例變數設置在物件上的，
you prepend them with the word self, with a full stop.
你將self放在他們單詞的前頭，加上句號。
In this definition of a person, for instance, we have written two methods.
例如，在此定義中的一個人，我們寫了兩種方法(method)。
Set name and set location.
設置名稱和設置的位置。
And both change instance bound variables, called name and location respectively.
這兩個變化實例綁定的變數，分別稱為名稱和位置。
When we run this cell, we see no output.
當我們運行此單元格時，我們沒有看到輸出。
The class exists, but we haven't created any objects yet.
class存在，但我們還沒有創建任何object。
We can instantiate this class by calling the class name with
我們可以具現化這個class，通過調用這個class名稱，
empty parenthesis behind it.
背後加空括號。
Then we can call functions and print out attributes of the class using the dot
然後我們可以調用它的函數功能，列印出class屬性，使用
notation, common in most languages.
點標記法(dot-notation)，這在大多數語言中是常見的。
There are a couple of implications of object-oriented programming in Python,
這裡有一些暗指含義，在Python的物件導向程式設計中，
that you should take away from this very brief example.
你應該可以從這個簡單的例子領會。
First, objects in Python do not have private or protected members.
首先，在Python中的物件不具有私有或受保護成員。
If you instantiate an object,
如果具現化一個物件，
you have full access to any of the methods or attributes of that object.
你對該物件的任何方法或屬性有完全存取權。
Second, there's no need for
第二，不需要
an explicit constructor when creating objects in Python.
用顯式的構造函數(constructor)，當創建Python的物件。
You can add a constructor if you want to by declaring the
如果你想要，你可以添加一個建構函式，通過聲明
__init__ method.
雙底線的方法。
Now I'm not going to dive any more into Python objects, because there's lots
我不想花太多時間在Python的物件(object)，因為有很多
of subtlety and, to be honest, most of the object oriented features of
微妙的地方，老實說，大多數物件導向程式的功能，
Python aren't really all that salient for introduction to data science.
在Python不是真的那麼重要，對資料科學入門的課來說。
If you're more interested,
如果你更有興趣，
I'd recommend checking out the Python documentation from the Python tutorial.
我建議您從Python教程中查看Python文檔。
It's fairly comprehensive overview of the object features of the language, and
這是對語言的object特徵相當完整的概述，並且
there will be a reference in the class resources.
將有一些參考資料在課程的資源中。
The map function is one of the basis for functional programming in Python.
Map函數是Python中函數程式語言的基礎之一。
Functional programming is a programming paradigm in which you explicitly declare
函數程式語言是一種程式範例，您在其中明確聲明
all parameters which could change through execution of a given function.
所有可以通過執行給定函數而改變的參數。
Thus functional programming is referred to as being side-effect free, because there
因此，函數程式語言被稱為沒有副作用的，因為
is a software contract that describes what can actually change by calling a function.
有一個軟體合約，規定當使用函數時，什麼是可以實際改變的。
Now, Python isn't a functional programming language in the pure sense.
現在，Python並不是純粹的函數程式語言。
Since you can have many side effects of functions, and certainly you don't have to
因為你可以有很多函數的副作用，並且你不一定非
pass in the parameters of everything that you're interested in changing.
傳遞一切參數你有興趣去改變的。
But functional programming causes one to think more heavily
但是函數程式語言使得一個人更加重視
while chaining operations together.
同時將操作連結在一起。
And this really is a sort of underlying theme in much of data science and
這真的是一種在很多資料科學的基本主題和
date cleaning in particular.
特別是資料的清理。
So, functional programming methods are often used in Python,
所以，函數程式語言方法經常在Python中使用，
and it's not uncommon to see a parameter for a function, be a function itself.
並且不是不常見到函數的參數，它們本身也是一個函數。
The map built-in function is one example of a functional programming feature
map內置功能是Python的函數程式語言功能的一個例子，
of Python, that I think ties together a number of aspects of the language.
我認為聯繫在一起這語言的一些方面。
The map function signature looks like this.
map的函數如下所示。
The first parameters of function that you want executed, and the second parameter,
第一個參數是你想要執行的函數，第二個參數，
and every following parameter, is something which can be iterated upon.
和下面的每個參數，是可以反覆運算後的東西。
All the iterable arguments are unpacked together, and
所有可反覆運算的參數都解開在一起，
passed into the given function.
傳遞到給定的函數。
That's a little cryptic, so let's take a look at an example.
這就是有點神秘，所以讓我們來看一個例子。
Imagine we have two list of numbers,
假設我們有兩個數字列表，
maybe prices from two different stores on exactly the same items.
也許從兩個不同的商店的價格，完全相同的項目。
And we wanted to find the minimum that we would have to pay
我們想找到我們必須支付的最低價，
if we bought the cheaper item between the two stores.
如果我們在兩家商店之間買到便宜的商品。
To do this, we could iterate through each list, comparing items and
要做到這一點，我們可以將遍歷每個列表，比較項目和
choosing the cheapest.
選擇最便宜的。
With map, we can do this comparison in a single statement.
用map，我們可以做這種比較在單個語句中。
But when we go to print out the map, we see that we get an odd reference value
但是，當我們去列印出來，我們看到我們得到奇怪的參考值
instead of a list of items that we're expecting.
而不是我們期待的項目列表。
This is called lazy evaluation.
這被稱為懶惰評估。
In Python, the map function returns to you a map object.
在Python中，map函數返回給你一個map物件(object)。
It doesn't actually try and run the function min on two items,
實際上並沒有嘗試在兩個項目上運行min函數，
until you look inside for a value.
直到你查看裡面的值。
This is an interesting design pattern of the language, and
這是一個有趣的語言設計模式，和
it's commonly used when dealing with big data.
它常用的在處理大資料時。
This allows us to have very efficient memory management,
這使得我們有非常有效的記憶體管理
even though something might be computationally complex.
即使是複雜的計算。
Maps are iterable, just like lists and tuples, so we can use a for
map是可以反覆運算，就像列表和元組，因此我們可以使用for迴圈
loop to look at all of the values in the map.
來查看map中的所有值。
This passing around of functions and data structures which they should be applied
這種傳遞函數和數據結構，應用到它們應該被用的，
to, is a hallmark of functional programming.
這是函數程式語言的標誌。
It's very common in data analysis and cleaning.
它是非常常見在數據分析和清理。
Here's a problem for you to try, that brings together some of the tasks
這裡是一個問題你可以嘗試，彙集了一些任務
you might be expecting to do with data cleaning.
你可能期待在資料清理去做。